But the core issue hasn't changed
Gu Group listed expected receivables
as available funds
but without a confirmation letter from the payer
The confirmation letter is in process
Then until it arrives
it can't be considered covered
Mr Fu did you study finance before
Not systematically
So you learned this at work
You read enough
and you pick up a bit
Did Mr Fu also
like reading documents this much as a kid
Mr Qin you make it sound like
you knew him as a child
I don't remember much from my childhood
That's fine
We can take our time finding out what you forgot
Mr Qin are you here today for the project
or for me
Both I actually came with a little
selfish intent to confirm something the Fu family
has spent years searching for
But if you're not willing
I won't push you
Let's finish the meeting first
Okay